A Guide to the Records of the Virginia Dept. for the Deaf and Hard of Hearing, 1972-2015
Library of Virginia
- Director's correspondence and subject files (Accession 41647), 1974-2001., Extent: 5 cubic feet. (Box 1-5)
  - National Association for State Relay Administration (NASRA), 1999-2000. (Box 5)
  - Two line voice carry over, 1999. (Box 5)
  - Smoke Detector Focus Group, 1998. (Box 5)
  - TTY modems, undated. (Box 5)
  - Technology demonstration centers, undated. (Box 5)
  - TEDPA/NASRA, 2000. (Box 5)
  - National Association of the Deaf (NAD), 2000. (Box 5)
  - Presentations / TAP table presentations, 2000. (Box 5)
- Director's correspondence and subject files (Accession 43273), 1974-1996., Extent: 3 cubic feet. (Box 1-8)
  This series is housed in 3 boxes and is arranged in original order. This series consists of the files of two Directors, Lily P. Bess and Susan Buckland. Records include correspondence, financial documentation, meeting files, projects files and reports. Includes VDDHH Advisory Board records, 1994-1996.
  - Director Buckland: Abingdon meeting, 1995 May. (Box 1)
  - Director Buckland: Disability Services Council meeting, 1995 June. (Box 1)
  - Director Buckland: Disability Services Council meeting, 1995 Aug. (Box 1)
  - Director Buckland: Disability Services Council meeting, 1995 Sept. (Box 1)
  - Director Buckland: Disability Services Council meeting, 1995 Dec. (Box 1)
  - Director Buckland: Disability Services Council meeting, 1996 Mar. (Box 1)
  - Director Buckland: Disability Services Council Survey, 1995 Aug. (Box 1)
  - Director Buckland: Disability Services Boards, 1995. (Box 1)
  - Director Buckland: Disability Services Boards - Members, 1995. (Box 1)
  - Director Buckland: Early Intervention Services for Infants and Toddlers with Disabilities and Their Families, 1995 Apr-May. (Box 1)
  - Director Buckland: Early Intervention Services for Infants and Toddlers with Disabilities and Their Families, 1995 May-June. (Box 1)
  - Director Buckland: Early Intervention Services for Infants and Toddlers with Disabilities and Their Families, 1996 Aug. (Box 1)
  - Director Buckland: Virginia Dept. of Education - Enrollment information, 1993. (Box 1)
  - Director Buckland: Virginia Quality Assurance Screening, 1995. (Box 1)
  - Director Buckland: Standards of Learing, 1995. (Box 1)
  - Director Buckland: Virginia Dept. of Education / VDDHH - Cooperative agreeement, 1996. (Box 1)
  - Director Buckland: Federal Shutdown - Continuing resolution, 1995. (Box 1)
  - Director Buckland: Fraternal Society for the Deaf - 15th Anniversary, 1995. (Box 1)
  - Director Buckland: Galladet University - Parents' Advisory Committee, 1994. (Box 1)
  - Director Buckland: Gunter and Sipple - Group getting deaf and hard of hearing Richmonders back together, 1995. (Box 1)
  - Director Buckland: Grievance procedures, 1995-1996. (Box 1)
  - Director Buckland: Aura Priola, 1995. (Box 1)
  - Director Buckland: Interpreter Programs Advisory Committee, 1995. (Box 1)
  - Director Buckland: Interpreter Training Guidelines, 1995. (Box 1)
  - Director Buckland: Outreach Programs, 1995. (Box 1)
  - Director Buckland: Outreach Specialists, 1994. (Box 1)
  - Director Buckland: Outreach - Office space, undated. (Box 1)
  - Director Buckland: Outreach policy guidelines, 1995. (Box 1)
  - Director Buckland: Outreach - Proposal for privatization, 1996. (Box 1)
  - Director Buckland: Developing training skills, 1996. (Box 1)
  - Director Buckland: Northern Virginia Resource Center, 1995. (Box 1)
  - Director Buckland: Northern Virginia Resource Center - Grang proposal, 1995. (Box 1)
  - Director Buckland: National Governors Association - Initiative of VDDHH on well being of children under 6, 1995. (Box 1)
  - Director Buckland: Motor Voter, 1995. (Box 1)
  - Director Buckland: Study of Mental Health Needs of the Deaf and Deaf-Blind Population of Virginia, 1986. (Box 1)
  - Director Buckland: Mental Health Plan, 1995. (Box 1)
  - Director Buckland: Mental Health Advisory Committee, 1994. (Box 1)
  - Director Buckland: Mental Health, 1995. (Box 1)
  - Director Buckland: Organization memberships, 1994. (Box 1)
  - Director Buckland: Legal workshop, 1995. (Box 1)
  - Director Buckland: Kansas Commission for the Deaf and Hard of Hearing, 1995. (Box 1)
  - Director Buckland: Improving Special Education Experiences, 1995-1996. (Box 1)
  - Director Buckland: Maternal and Child Health Service block grants, 1995. (Box 1)
  - Director Buckland: Community Work Experience Program, 1996. (Box 1)
  - Director Buckland: Participants, Not Spectators, 1994-1995. (Box 1)
  - Director Buckland: Peninsula Center for Independent Living, 1995. (Box 1)
  - Director Buckland: Empowerment speech - Soar Like Eagles, 1995. (Box 1)
  - Director Buckland: President's Committee on Employment of People with Disabilities, 1994. (Box 1)
  - Director Buckland: Disabilities Services Council meeting, 1994 Nov. (Box 1)
  - Director Buckland: Local Disability Services Boards - Call, undated. (Box 1)
  - Director Buckland: Local Disability Services Boards - Applications, 1995. (Box 1)
  - Director Buckland: Virginia Board for People with Disabilities, 1994. (Box 1)
  - Director Buckland: Rehabilitative Services Incentive Funds - Grants, 1998. (Box 1)
  - Director Buckland: Communication Centers for the Deaf, 1995. (Box 1)
  - Director Buckland: VDDHH Advisory Board - Biographies, undated. (Box 1)
  - Director Buckland: VDDHH Advisory Board - Goals and Vision, 1995. (Box 1)
  - Director Buckland: VDDHH Advisory Board - Special meeting, 1994 Apr. (Box 1)
  - Director Buckland: VDDHH Advisory Board - Meeting, 1994 Oct. (Box 1)
  - Director Buckland: VDDHH Advisory Board - Meeting, 1994 Dec. (Box 1)
  - Director Buckland: VDDHH Advisory Board - Meeting, 1995 Feb. (Box 1)
  - Director Buckland: VDDHH Advisory Board - Meeting, 1995 May. (Box 1)
  - Director Buckland: VDDHH Advisory Board - Meeting, 1996 Feb. (Box 1)
  - Director Buckland: VDDHH Advisory Board - Meeting, 1996 May. (Box 1)
  - Director Buckland: VDDHH Advisory Board - Meeting, 1996 Aug. (Box 1)
  - Director Buckland: Schowe, Ben - Correspondence, 1995. (Box 1)
  - Director Buckland: Agency Four Year Strategic Plan, undated. (Box 1)
  - Director Buckland: Benchmark Budget - Andrews/Ball (1996-1998), 1995. (Box 1)
  - Director Buckland: RFP / Secretary of Administration / Waiver, 1995. (Box 1)
  - Director Buckland: RFP / Dept. of Information Technology, 1995. (Box 1)
  - Director Buckland: Welfare recipients, 1995. (Box 1)
  - Director Buckland: Americans with Disabilities Act, 1995. (Box 1)
  - Director Buckland: Expo Steering Committee, 1996. (Box 1)
  - Director Buckland: Dept. for the Aging - Long-term care, 1996. (Box 1)
  - Director Buckland: FYI / Miscellaneous, 1995. (Box 1)
  - Director Buckland: Telecommunications Relay Service / Norton, 1995. (Box 2)
  - Director Buckland: Telecommunications Relay Service / Norton - State Corporation Commission, 1995. (Box 2)
  - Director Buckland: Telecommunications Relay Service / Norton - Code changes, 1995. (Box 2)
  - Director Bess: Form A1 Non-general Fund Revenue, 1984. (Box 2)
  - Director Bess: Form A2 Non-general Fund Revenue - Six Year Forecast, 1984. (Box 2)
  - Director Bess: Federal Budget Impact Identification, 1981. (Box 2)
  - Director Bess: Summaries of Accounts Receivables/Payables Year End Report, 1981. (Box 2)
  - Director Bess: Year End Financial Statement, 1981. (Box 2)
  - Director Bess: Form 27 Appropriations/Operating Plan Adjustment, 1982. (Box 2)
  - Director Bess: For E-1 Resource Request Forecast, 1981. (Box 2)
  - Director Bess: Form F-1 and E-2 Addemdum Request, 1981. (Box 2)
  - Director Bess: Faithful Performance Duty Blanket Bond, 1981. (Box 2)
  - Director Bess: Treasury loans, 1981. (Box 2)
  - Director Bess: Method for financial coordination of interpreter services, 1980. (Box 2)
  - Director Bess: Dept. of General Services Directive 1-81, 1981. (Box 2)
  - Director Bess: Dept. of Planning and Budget Directive 8-80 (Indirect Cost Recoveries), 1981. (Box 2)
  - Director Bess: Financial proposal, 1983. (Box 2)
  - Director Bess: Research materials, undated. (Box 2)
  - VDDHH Advisory Board - Members, 1996. (Box 1)
  - Director Bess: Modeling the Career Development of Hearing and Hearing Impaired Adolescents (dissertation), 1986. (Box 2)
  - Director Bess: VDDHH Outreach Workers Orientation, 1986. (Box 2)
  - Director Bess: Executive Agreement Status Report, 1983-1984. (Box 2)
  - Director Bess: J. Sargeant Reynolds Community College - Interpreter Training Program, 1986. (Box 2)
  - Director Bess: Operating Budget, 1985-1986. (Box 2)
  - Director Bess: Executive Agreement, 1984-1986. (Box 2)
  - Director Bess: Presentations to parent groups, undated. (Box 2)
  - Director Bess: Secretary of Human Resources, 1983. (Box 2)
  - Director Bess: Secretary of Human Resources, 1984. (Box 2)
  - Director Bess: Proposal for Deaf Programs, 1981. (Box 2)
  - Director Bess: Special Policy Work Group, 1987. (Box 2)
  - Director Bess: Self Advocacy, undated. (Box 2)
  - Director Bess: Staunton Center for the Deaf, 1980-1981. (Box 2)
  - Director Bess: Southwestern Virginia Training Center, 1977-1979. (Box 2)
  - Director Bess: Insurance, 1976-1981. (Box 2)
  - Director Bess: Virginia School for the Deaf and Blind, 1980-1981. (Box 2)
  - Director Bess: Interpreter training, 1974-1977. (Box 2)
  - Director Bess: Shiflett, Jean, 1975-1977. (Box 2)
  - Director Bess: Shafer, Elaine, 1978-1979. (Box 2)
  - Director Bess: Supreme Court, 1980. (Box 2)
  - Director Bess: Social Security, 1981. (Box 2)
  - Director Bess: Vocational Rehabilitation - Disability Determination, 1977. (Box 2)
  - Director Bess: Housing, 1976-1981. (Box 2)
  - Director Bess: Hospitals, 1975-1979. (Box 2)
  - Director Bess: Employment, 1975-1982. (Box 2)
  - Director Bess: Arts, 197-1978. (Box 2)
  - Director Bess: Alcoholism, 1979-1980. (Box 3)
  - Director Bess: Aging, 1980-1983. (Box 3)
  - Director Bess: Public Hearing (HJR 162), 1980. (Box 3)
  - Director Bess: Miscellaneous, 1977-1986. (Box 3)
  - Director Bess: Survey of States with Community Service Centers, 1984. (Box 3)
  - Director Bess: Statistics, undated. (Box 3)
  - Director Bess: Correspondence, 1980-1981. (Box 3)
  - Director Bess: Correspondence, 1978-1980. (Box 3)
  - Director Bess: Miscellaneous, 1978-1979. (Box 3)
  - Director Bess: Virginia Council for the Deaf - Awards, 1978. (Box 3)
  - Director Bess: Development of ISP Program System, 1983. (Box 3)
  - Director Bess: Small agency heads, undated. (Box 3)
  - Director Bess: Positions on Accessibility for Deaf People, undated. (Box 3)
  - Director Bess: Western State Hospital, undated. (Box 3)
  - Director Bess: Plans for a Registry of State Schools for the Deaf, 1982-1983. (Box 3)
  - Director Bess: Study Report of State Schools for the Deaf, 1983. (Box 3)
  - Director Bess: Future training dates, 1983. (Box 3)
  - Director Bess: Sample of issue needs and problems for the deaf, 1978. (Box 3)
  - Director Bess: New initiatives and budget calendar, 1983. (Box 3)
  - Director Bess: Human Resources, Office of, 1982-1983. (Box 3)
  - Director Bess: Prevention in Human Resources, 1985. (Box 3)
  - Director Bess: Governor's Overall Advisory Council, 1984-1985. (Box 3)
  - Director Bess: Sample letters, 1983-1984. (Box 3)
  - Director Bess: Mandated studies (legislation), 1983. (Box 3)
  - Director Bess: Interpreter Services funding, undated. (Box 3)
  - Director Bess: Legislative coordination process, 1984. (Box 3)
  - Director Bess: Budget reductions for the Virginia Council for the Deaf, 1983. (Box 3)
  - Director Bess: Adjusted appropriations, 1983-1984. (Box 3)
  - Director Bess: Drafting letters for the Governor - Policy, 1983-1984. (Box 3)
  - Director Bess: Governor's Overall Advisory Committee - PR Committee, 1985. (Box 3)
  - Director Bess: Human Resources - Budget presentation to Senate Finance Committee and House Appropriations Committee, 1983. (Box 3)
  - Director Bess: Human Resources - Review of bills for Governor, 1983. (Box 3)
  - Director Bess: Human Resources - Federal priorities, 1982. (Box 3)
  - Director Bess: Concept and Services of Community Service Centers for the Deaf, 1985. (Box 3)
  - Director Bess: Rubella deaf, 1984. (Box 3)
  - Director Bess: JLARC recommendations, 1983. (Box 3)
  - Director Bess: Silent Network, 1985. (Box 3)
  - Director Bess: Committee on Housing for the Disabled, 1984-1985. (Box 3)
  - Director Bess: Committee on Housing for the Disabled, 1985. (Box 3)
  - Director Bess: General Assembly, 1984. (Box 3)
  - Director Bess: Pink sheets, 1983. (Box 3)
  - Director Bess: Study of the Feasibility of Combining the Virginia Council for the Deaf and Virginia Commission for the Visually Handicapped into a Single Agency (v. II), 1979. (Box 3)
  - Director Bess: Governor's Overall Advisory Committee - PR Committee, 1984-1985. (Box 3)
  - Director Bess: Washington Liaison Office, 1977-1979. (Box 3)
  - Director Bess: Workshop on Improving Delivery of Services to the Deaf, 1976. (Box 3)
  - Director Bess: Cluster concept, 1983-1984. (Box 3)
- Director's correspondence and subject files (Accession 52778), 1973-2015., Extent: 8 cubic feet. (Box 1-8)
  This series is housed in 8 boxes and is arranged in original order. This series consists of the files of several Directors, Acting Directors and Deputy Directors, including Ronald Lanier (4 cu. ft.), as well as J. Rex Purvis, F.P. Yates, Lily P. Bess, Wayne Shoot, Kathy Vesley, William Hill, Clayton Bowen and Susan Buckland (2 cu. ft.). Records include correspondence, financial documentation, meeting files, projects file and reports.
  - Director Lanier: Sample annual report - Tennessee Council for the Hearing Impaired (FY 1990), 1990-1991. (Box 1)
  - Director Lanier: SKI HI Project, 1990. (Box 1)
  - Director Lanier: Project RATE, 1992. (Box 1)
  - Director Lanier: Syposium on Counseling Needs, 1992. (Box 1)
  - Director Lanier: Historical newspaper clippings, 1990-1992. (Box 1)
  - Director Lanier: Project TAPE, 1992. (Box 1)
  - Director Lanier: VATS Grant, 1993. (Box 1)
  - Director Lanier: Policy and procedures manual, 1994. (Box 1)
  - Director Lanier: Strategic plan and budget package, 1997. (Box 1)
  - Director Lanier: Lanier appointment, 1997. (Box 1)
  - Director Lanier: Legislative studies, 1997-1998. (Box 1)
  - Director Lanier: Performance measures, 1997-1998. (Box 1)
  - Director Lanier: Secretary of Health and Human Resources, 1997-1998. (Box 1)
  - Director Lanier: Relay Program, 1997-2000. (Box 1)
  - Director Lanier: Dept. of Rehabilitative Services Cooperative Agreement and Memorandum of Understanding, 1997-2004. (Box 1)
  - Director Lanier: Secretary of Health and Human Resources, 1997-2007. (Box 1)
  - Director Lanier: Project documentation and studies, 1997-2008. (Box 1)
  - Director Lanier: VDDHH Conference, 1998. (Box 1)
  - Director Lanier: Consolidated D/A Services Agencies / DRS internal audit, 1998. (Box 1)
  - Director Lanier: Newsletters, 1998. (Box 1)
  - Director Lanier: Town Hall meetings, 1998. (Box 1)
  - Director Lanier: Cooperative agreements and contractural obligations, 1998. (Box 1)
  - Director Lanier: Letters of recommendations, 1998-1999. (Box 1)
  - Director Lanier: Legislative Actions Summary, 1998-2000. (Box 1)
  - Director Lanier: Dept. of Corrections, 1998-2002. (Box 1)
  - Director Lanier: Strategic planning, 1998-2004. (Box 1)
  - Director Lanier: VDDHH Outreach Program, 1998-2002. (Box 2)
  - Director Lanier: Dept. for Aging, 1998, 2005. (Box 2)
  - Director Lanier: General correspondence, 1998-2009. (Box 2)
  - Director Lanier: Correspondence with other state agencies, 1998-2009. (Box 2)
  - Director Lanier: Dept. of Rehabilitative Services, 1998-2011. (Box 2)
  - Director Lanier: Office of the Attorney General, 1998-2011. (Box 2)
  - Director Lanier: VDDHH Relay Program, 1998-2011. (Box 2)
  - Director Lanier: Dept. for Allied Health, 2009. (Box 2)
  - Director Lanier: Media alerts, 1999. (Box 2)
  - Director Lanier: Secretary of Health and Human Resources, 1999-2000. (Box 2)
  - Director Lanier: VDDHH Interpreter and Quality Assurance Programs, 1999-2004. (Box 2)
  - Director Lanier: Dept. of Planning and Budget, 1999-2005. (Box 2)
  - Director Lanier: Surveys - Administration, 1999-2009. (Box 2)
  - Director Lanier: Productivity savings, 2000. (Box 2)
  - Director Lanier: Annual reports, 2006. (Box 2)
  - Director Lanier: Secretary of Health and Human Resources, 2001. (Box 3)
  - Director Lanier: Dept. of Motor Vehicles, 2001-2003. (Box 3)
  - Director Lanier: Virginia Association for the Deaf - Conference, 2001, 2004, 2007. (Box 3)
  - Director Lanier: Administrative files, 2001-2008. (Box 3)
  - Director Lanier: Legislative files, 2001-2009. (Box 3)
  - Director Lanier: PREP Project, 2002. (Box 3)
  - Director Lanier: Secretary of Health and Human Resources, 2002-2010. (Box 3)
  - Director Lanier: Virginia Schools for the Deaf - Consolidation, 2003-2005. (Box 3)
  - Director Lanier: Virginia Association for the Deaf, 2003-2009. (Box 3)
  - Director Lanier: Technology Assistance Program, 2003-2008. (Box 3)
  - Director Lanier: Virginia Commonwealth University, 2003-2011. (Box 3)
  - Director Lanier: Office of the Attorney General, 2004. (Box 3)
  - Director Lanier: Dept. of Planning and Budget, 2006-2008. (Box 3)
  - Director Lanier: VDDHH Conference, 2007. (Box 3)
  - Director Lanier: Administrative correspondence, 2011. (Box 3)
  - Director Lanier: Virginia Statewide Independent Living Council, 2011. (Box 3)
  - Director Lanier: Virginia Commonwealth University - Rehabilitation Counseling, 2010-2012. (Box 3)
  - Director Lanier: Administrative files, 2011. (Box 3)
  - Director Lanier: Administrative files, 2012. (Box 3)
  - Director Lanier: Administrative files, 2013. (Box 3)
  - Director Lanier: State Interagency Team (SIT), 2013. (Box 3)
  - Director Lanier: Administrative files, 2014. (Box 3)
  - Director Lanier: Virginia Board for People with Disabilities, 2008-2014. (Box 3)
  - Director Lanier: Administrative files, 2015. (Box 3)
  - Director Lanier: Richmond Mayor's Youth Academy, 2015. (Box 3)
  - Director Lanier: Mental Health Needs of the Deaf - Training workshop, 1977 May. (Box 4)
  - Director Lanier: Virginia Dept. for the Deaf and Hard of Hearing Profile, 1989 Aug. (Box 4)
  - Director Lanier: Report on the Special Needs of Persons who are Hard of Hearing, 1989 Dec. (Box 4)
  - Director Lanier: Audit of Agencies Serving Virginians with Disabilities (APA), 2000 June. (Box 4)
  - Director Lanier: Audit of Agencies Serving Virginians with Disabilities (APA), 2002 June. (Box 4)
  - Director Lanier: Virginia Schools for the Deaf and Blind (VSDB) Consolidation Task Force, 2003 June. (Box 4)
  - Director Lanier: VSDB Consolidation Task Force, 2003 July. (Box 4)
  - Director Lanier: VSDB Consolidation Task Force, 2003 Aug. (Box 4)
  - Director Lanier: Audit of Agencies Serving Virginians with Disabilities (APA), 2004 June. (Box 4)
  - Director Lanier: VSDB Consolidation Task Force, 2002-2004. (Box 4)
  - Director Lanier: Advisory Council on Mental Health Services for Persons who are Deaf, Hard of Hearing, or Deaf-Blind - Finance report, 1993-1995. (Box 4)
  - Director Purvis: Correspondence, 1973-1974. (Box 5)
  - Issues/Background papers, 1975-1976. (Box 5)
  - Director Yates: Correspondence, 1974-1981. (Box 5)
  - Director Yates: Correspondence, 1973-1982. (Box 5)
  - Director Yates: Virginia Registry of Interpreters for the Deaf (VRID), 1974-1984. (Box 5)
  - Director Yates: Virginia Schools for the Deaf, 1974-1984. (Box 5)
  - Director Bess: Correspondence, 1985-1987. (Box 5)
  - Director Bess: Correspondence, 1978-1990. (Box 5)
  - Director Bess: Correspondence (Education), 1988-1992. (Box 5)
  - Director Bess: Testimony for General Assembly, 1986-1988. (Box 5)
  - Director Bess: Northern Virginia Community Center, 1985-1986. (Box 5)
  - Director Bess: VDDHH Code information, 1988-1991. (Box 5)
  - Director Bess: Legislative proposals, 1987-1988. (Box 5)
  - Director Shook: Deaf Juror, 1988. (Box 5)
  - Director Corresondence:, 1990-1993. (Box 5)
  - Agency Head legislative information, 1982-1999. (Box 5)
  - Agency Head correspondence, 1983-1998. (Box 5)
  - Director Bess: Correspondence, 1981-1990. (Box 6)
  - Director Bess: Correspondence, 1985-1989. (Box 6)
  - Deputy Director Hill: Correspondence, 1987-1996. (Box 6)
  - Deputy Director Vesley: Correspondence, 1986-1990. (Box 6)
  - Deputy Director Vesley: Correspondence, 1993. (Box 6)
  - Acting Director Bowen: Correspondence and Board meeting, 1993-1994, 1997. (Box 6)
  - Acting Director Bowen: Correspondence, 1993-1994. (Box 6)
  - Director Buckland: Correspondence and Board meetings, 1994-1996. (Box 6)
  - Director Buckland: Stakeholders, 1994-1996. (Box 6)
  - Director Buckland: Correspondence and resource training, 1994-1996. (Box 6)
  - Director Buckland: Correspondence, 1994-1996. (Box 6)
  - General Assembly, 1989-1992. (Box 7)
  - Governor's Office Executive Memos, 1982-1993. (Box 7)
  - Grants - Developmental disabilities, 1991-1996. (Box 7)
  - Hard of Hearing Legislative Study, 1988-1990. (Box 7)
  - Hard of Hearing Task Force, 1989. (Box 7)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources, 1990-1993. (Box 7)
  - Administrative correspondence - Secretary's Office, 1974-1986. (Box 8)
  - Administrative correspondence, 1982-1989. (Box 8)
  - Administrative correspondence, 1990-1994. (Box 8)
  - Affirmative action issues, 1987-1991. (Box 8)
  - Agencies - Working Together Model, 2005-2006. (Box 8)
  - Aging, Dept. of - Correspondence, 1982-1989. (Box 8)
  - Aging, Dept. of - Administrative file, 1990-1993. (Box 8)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts, 1981-1996. (Box 8)
  - Beyer Commission Public Hearings, 1991 June. (Box 8)
  - Commerce, Dept. of, 1989-1990. (Box 8)
  - Commission on Government Reform - Strikeforce, 1994. (Box 8)
  - Committee Minutes - General information, 1988-1991. (Box 8)
  - Commonwealth, Secretary of, 1977-1992. (Box 8)
  - Communications access, 1991-1993. (Box 8)
  - Communications Center for the Deaf, 1984-1997. (Box 8)
  - Communications and Assistive Technology Services, 1992. (Box 8)
  - Community Services Board, 1985-1994. (Box 8)
  - Comptroller, Office of the, 1982-1995. (Box 8)
  - Community Work Experience Project, 1995. (Box 8)
  - Crestar Bank, 1995. (Box 8)
  - DHMRSAS - Part B Interagency Agreement, 1993. (Box 8)
  - Danville Community College, 1996. (Box 8)
  - Deaf Awareness Week, 1994. (Box 8)
  - Deaf Community Counseling Service, 1981-1992. (Box 8)
  - Deaf inmates, 1976-1996. (Box 8)
  - Deaf Rally at the Capital, 1986. (Box 8)
  - Deaf Registry - Correspondence, 1975-1991. (Box 8)
  - Demographic studies, 1974-1988. (Box 8)